[
  {
    "question": "Das Messer",
    "answer": "Το μαχαίρι",
    "phonetic": "To mach**ái**ri"
  },
  {
    "question": "Die Gabel",
    "answer": "Το πιρούνι",
    "phonetic": "To piro**ú**ni"
  },
  {
    "question": "Der Löffel",
    "answer": "Το κουτάλι",
    "phonetic": "To kout**á**li"
  },
  {
    "question": "Das Brot",
    "answer": "Το ψωμί",
    "phonetic": "To psom**í**"
  },
  {
    "question": "Die Gemüse",
    "answer": "Τα λαχανικά",
    "phonetic": "Ta lachanik**á**"
  },
  {
    "question": "Der Teller",
    "answer": "Το πιάτο",
    "phonetic": "To pi**á**to"
  },
  {
    "question": "Das Glas",
    "answer": "Το ποτήρι",
    "phonetic": "To pot**í**ri"
  },
  {
    "question": "Der Pfeffer",
    "answer": "Το πιπέρι",
    "phonetic": "To pip**é**ri"
  },
  {
    "question": "Das Salz",
    "answer": "Το αλάτι",
    "phonetic": "To al**á**ti"
  },
  {
    "question": "Der Zucker",
    "answer": "Η ζάχαρη",
    "phonetic": "I **zá**chari"
  },
  {
    "question": "Das Mehl",
    "answer": "Το αλεύρι",
    "phonetic": "To al**év**ri"
  },
  {
    "question": "der Eiswürfel",
    "answer": "Ο παγάκος",
    "phonetic": "O pag**á**kos"
  },
  {
    "question": "Das Fleisch",
    "answer": "Το κρέας",
    "phonetic": "To **kré**as"
  },
  {
    "question": "das Hühnchen",
    "answer": "Το κοτόπουλο",
    "phonetic": "To kot**ó**poulo"
  },
  {
    "question": "Der Fisch",
    "answer": "Το ψάρι",
    "phonetic": "To ps**á**ri"
  },
  {
    "question": "das Steak",
    "answer": "Η μπριζόλα",
    "phonetic": "I briz**ó**la"
  },
  {
    "question": "Der Essig",
    "answer": "Το ξίδι",
    "phonetic": "To **xí**di"
  },
  {
    "question": "Das Olivenöl",
    "answer": "Το ελαιόλαδο",
    "phonetic": "To elai**ó**lado"
  },
  {
    "question": "das öl",
    "answer": "Το λάδι",
    "phonetic": "To **lá**di"
  },
  {
    "question": "Die Zwiebel",
    "answer": "Το κρεμμύδι",
    "phonetic": "To kremm**ý**di"
  },
  {
    "question": "Das Ei",
    "answer": "Το αυγό",
    "phonetic": "To avg**ó**"
  },
  {
    "question": "Die Paprika",
    "answer": "Η πιπεριά",
    "phonetic": "I piperi**á**"
  },
  {
    "question": "Die Gurke",
    "answer": "Το αγγούρι",
    "phonetic": "To ang**oú**ri"
  }
]
